Ivan Adamovich

Junior Front-end Software Engineer

Contacts

Minsk, Belarus | **Phone**: (A1) +375-(29)-146-55-56 | **Email**: ivanadams1998@gmail.com **GitHub**: github.com/Ivan-Adamovich | **Linkedin**: linkedin.com/in/ivan-adamovich/

About me

I am a Junior JavaScript Software Engineer in Front-end. My practical experience is more than 6 months. My goals are constantly learning and developing. Now i practice TypeScript, React + Redux and improve my English skills. I like to work as a team and solve interesting problems.

Education

REPUBLICAN INSTITUTE OF PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION | MINSK STATE AUTOMECHANICAL COLLEGE | 2017

- · Car maintenance and repair
- · 3rd category car mechanic

Training courses

ITCITY.BY | UX/UI DESIGN + HTML/CSS | 2020

UDEMY.COM | JAVASCRIPT FOR BEGINNERS | 2022

UDEMY.COM | JAVASCRIPT + REACT + REDUX | 2022

UDEMY.COM | TYPESCRIPT FOR BEGINNERS | 2022

Skills and technologies

HADD

HARD	SOFT
· HTML + CSS / SCSS / SASS	· UX / UI
· JavaScript / TypeScript	· Figma / Sketch
· React	\cdot Adobe Photoshop / Illustrator
· Redux	· Tilda
· Git / GitHub	·Scrum
· Bootstrap / Material UI	· English (A2)

COET

Work experience

FRONT-END DEVELOPER | SCOUTLIKE | JULY 2022 - DECEMBER 2022

Service for football clubs and players that helps to communicate and sign contracts without any personal agent.

Responsibilities:

- · UI component development with React.js (hooks)
- · Using the material UI library
- · Creating adaptive and flexible layouts for desktop and mobile devices
- · Using npm packages, git and webpack

GRAPHIC AND UX/UI DESIGNER | FREELANCE | MAY 2020 – MAY 2022

Freelance

Responsibilities:

- · Designing user interfaces of multi-page websites and landing-pages
- · Creation websites with the Tilda
- · Development of content for advertising on social networks
- · Design of printed products
- · Creation of logos

SALES MANAGER | VINCODEAUTO | MARCH 2018 - JANUARY 2020

Online auto parts store

Responsibilities:

- · Working with CRM
- · Counseling clients
- · Formation of orders
- · Sales